Noemely Alcantara

11500 NW 14th Ct. Pembroke Pines, FL 33026 | C: (646)-812-6771 | Noemelyalcantara@yahoo.com

SUMMARY

I am currently enrolled in Miami International University of Art and Design. While in pursuit of my career in the arts, I strive to fill my days learning and gaining experience through opportunities that will push me to be a hardworking, dedicated, and well-rounded person.

HIGHLIGHTS

- Enjoys Interacting with different types of people
- Understanding and cooperative team member
- Microsoft word, Power Point, Photo Shop, Illustrator
- Painting and drawing skills
- Creative
- CPR certified

EDUCATION

Miami International University of Art and Design Graphic and Web Design Major

JOB EXPERIENCE

KidsWorld Volunteer Coordinator at Oasis Church 2014-7/2015

- ✓ Scheduling Volunteers
- ✓ Coordinating Volunteer Events (trainings, celebrations, meetings etc.)
- ✓ Providing training for all volunteers
- ✓ Keeping Volunteers updated and appreciated

KidsWorld Classroom Experience Coordinator 5/2016-present

- ✓ Prepare and Implement curriculum from ages 2-10.
- ✓ Plan and execute creative environments for facilities used
- ✓ Schedule and hold creative meetings.

David Posnack Jewish Community Center 3/2014-10/2014

I was given the authority to take charge of a preschool class 5 times a week. Having this job made me accountable of every child's safety.